Guide to the Taube Archive of the International Military Tribunal (IMT) at Nuremberg mt839rq8746
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- International Military Tribunal (IMT) at Nuremberg - Document Books, DocBooks; International Military Tribunal
  - U.S. Document Book L: Aggressive War - Opening Statement, H-1119; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - U.S. Document Book M: 1933 - 1936 Preparation for Aggression, H-1120; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - U.S. Document Book N: Aggression against Austria, H-1121; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - U.S. Document Book N, Supplement: Aggression against Austria, H-1122; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - U.S. Document Book O: Aggressive War: Execution of the Plan to invade Czechoslovakia, H-1123; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - U.S. Document Book P: The Nazi Conspirators' War of Aggression against the U.S.S.R., H-1124; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - U.S. Document Book Q: Collaboration with Italy and Japan and Aggressive War against the United States, H-1125; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - U.S. Document Book R: The Nazi Conspirators' Slave Labor program, the Illegal use of Prisoners of War, and special responsibility of Defendants Sauckel and Speer therefor, H-1126; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - U.S. Document Book S: Concentration Camps, H-1127; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) Photograph of chart "Concentration Camps" inserted
  - U.S. Document Book T (Vol. 1): Persecution of the Jews, H-1128; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - U.S. Document Book T (Vol. 2): Persecution of the Jews, H-1129; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - U.S. Document Book U: Germanization and Spoliation, H-1131; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - U.S. Document Book V: Criminality of Das Korps der Politischen Leiter der National-sozialistischen Deutschen Arbeiterpartei (Leadership Corps of the Nazi Party.), H-1132; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - U.S. Document Book W: Plunder of Art Treasures, H-1134; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - U.S. Document Book X: Die Reichsregierung (Reich Cabinet), H-1136; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - U.S. Document Book Y: Criminality of the Sturmabteilungen (the SA) of the National Socialist German Labor Party, H-1138; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - U.S. Document Book Z, Vol. I: The SS, H-1140; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - U.S. Document Book Z, Vol. II: The SS, H-1141; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - U.S. Document Book CC, Vol. I: General Staff & High Command Group, H-1143; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - U.S. Document Book CC, Vol. II: General Staff & High Command Group, H-1144; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - U.S. Document Book CC, Vol. III: General Staff & High Command Group, H-1145; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - U.S. Document Book DD, Vol. I: The Individual Responsibility of the Defendant Hermann GOERING for Crimes Against Peace, War Crimes and Crimes Against Humanity, H-1146; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - U.S. Document Book DD, Vol. II: The Individual Responsibility of the Defendant Hermann GOERING for Crimes Against Peace, War Crimes and Crimes Against Humanity, H-1147; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - British Document Book No. 1: Treaties in general, H-1150; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - British Document Book No. 2: Count 2, Poland, Danzig, England, France, H-1151; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - British Document Book No. 3: Aggression against Norway & Denmark, H-1152; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - British Document Book No. 4: Aggression against Belgium, Netherlands & Luxembourg, H-1153; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - British Document Book No. 5: Aggression against Greece & Yugoslavia, H-1154; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - British Document Book No. 6: Joachim von RIBBENTROP, H-1155; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - British Document Book No. 7: Wilhelm KEITEL and Alfred JODL, H-1157; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - British Document Book No. 7 A: Alfred JODL, H-1158; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - British Document Book No. 8: Julius STREICHER, H-1161; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - British Document Book No. 9: Karl DOENITZ, H-1163; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - British Document Book No. 10: Erich RAEDER, H-1165; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - British Document Book No. 10 A: Erich RAEDER, H-1166; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - British Document Book No. 11: Franz von PAPEN, H-1168; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - British Document Book No. 11 A: Franz von PAPEN, H-1169; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - British Document Book No. 12: Constantin von NEURATH, H-1171; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - British Document Book No. 12 A: Constantin von NEURATH, H-1172; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - British Document Book No. 12 B: Constantin von NEURATH, H-1173; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - British Document Book No. 13: Rudolf HESS, H-1175; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - British Document Book: Rudolf HESS, Addendum, H-1176; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - British Document Book: Cross-Examination – Miscellaneous, H-1178; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) 151 pages
  - U.S. Document Book AA, Vol. I Gestapo & SD, H-1219; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - U.S. Document Book AA, Vol. II Gestapo & SD, H-1220; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - U.S. Document Book BB: Ernst KALTENBRUNNER, H-1222; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) contents bound in 4 parts
  - U.S. Document Book DD, Vol. III: The Individual Responsibility of the Defendant Hermann GOERING for Crimes Against Peace, War Crimes and Crimes Against Humanity, H-1224; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) 22 loose sheets inserted
  - U.S. Document Book EE: Alfred ROSENBERG, H-1225; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) 101 loose sheets inserted
  - U.S. Document Book FF: Hans FRANK, H-1226; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - U.S. Document Book GG, The Individual Responsibility of the Defendant Hjalmar SCHACHT, H-1228; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) contents bound in 2 parts; 18 loose sheets inserted in the 1st part
  - U.S. Document Book GG Supplement, The Individual Responsibility of the Defendant Hjalmar SCHACHT, H-1229; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) Insertion of loose documents as follows: 32 pages (French), 37 pages (Russian), 3 pages (German)
  - U.S. Document Book HH: The Individual Responsibility of the Defendant Walter FUNK for Crimes Against Peace and Crimes Against Humanity, H-1231; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) 15 pages inserted as loose documents
  - U.S. Document Book II: The Individual Responsibility of the Defendant Baldur von SCHIRACH, H-1233; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - U.S. Document Book JJ: Martin BORMANN, H-1235; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) 2 loose sheets inserted
  - U.S. Document Book KK against the Defendant Arthur SEYSS-INQUART, H-1237; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) contents bound in 2 parts
  - U.S. Document Book LL: Wilhelm FRICK, H-1239; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) 13 loose sheets inserted
  - U.S. Document Book MM: The Individual Responsibility of the Defendant Hans FRITZSCHE for Crimes Against Peace, War Crimes and Crimes Against Humanity, H-1241; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) Insertion of loose documents as follows: 49 pages (French), 24 pages (Russian)
  - USSR Document Book 5a, H-1465; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - USSR Document Book 5b, H-1466; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - USSR Document Book 5c, H-1467; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - USSR Document Book 6 & 6a, H-1468; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - USSR Document Book 6b, H-1469; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - USSR Document Book 7, H-1470; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - USSR Document Book 7a, H-1471; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - USSR Document Book 8, H-1472; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - USSR Document Book 1, H-1518; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - USSR Document Book 2, H-1519; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - USSR Document Book 4, H-1520; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - USSR Document Book 5, H-1521; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Alfred JODL No. 1, H-1711; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Alfred JODL No. 2, H-1712; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - Alfred JODL No. 3, H-1713; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - SD Document Book, H-2710; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) Certificate (at front of Book) signed by Defense Counsel Dr. Gawlik. Notation on Folder: "File with Exhibits; (No individual exhibits.)"
  - French Document Book: Copies handed to Judges, 18 January 1946, 1946-01-18; H-5010; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - French Document Book: Report of Ministry of Prisoners, Deportees, Refugees and Prisoners of War, H-5011; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) 61 pages
  - French Document Book: General Observations (Economic), H-5013; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - French Document Book: Denmark (Economic), H-5015; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - French Document Book: Norway (Economic), H-5017; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - French Document Book: Holland (Economic), H-5019; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - French Document Book: Belgium (Economic), H-5021; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - French Document Book: Luxembourg (Economic), H-5022; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - French Document Book: France (Economic) (Documents 203-222), H-5024; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - French Document Book: France (Economic) (Marked "Duplicate 203-222"), H-5025; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - French Document Book: France (Economic) (Documents 223, 230-264), H-5026; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) 170 loose pages
  - French Document Book: France (Economic) (Marked "Duplicate 223-264"), H-5027; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) 173 loose pages
  - French Document Book: Hemmen Report I, H-5028; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - French Document Book: Hemmen Report II, H-5029; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - French Document Book: Hemmen Report III, H-5030; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - French Document Book: Hemmen Report IV, H-5031; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - French Document Book: Hemmen Report V, H-5032; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - French Document Book: Hemmen Report VI, H-5033; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - French Document Book: Hostages, H-5037; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - French Document Book: German Justice in Occupied Western Territories - France, H-5039; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - French Document Book: Deposition of Witnesses - France, H-5040; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - French Document Book: German Justice in occupied Norway, Belgium, Holland & Luxembourg, H-5041; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - French Document Book I - Deportation, H-5043; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - French Document Book II - Concentration Camps, H-5044; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) pp. 1-250
  - French Document Book II - Concentration Camps, Annex, H-5045; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) 35 pages
  - French Document Book: Prisoners of War, H-5047; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) pp. 1-133
  - French Document Book: Prisoners of War - Supplement, H-5048; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - French Document Book: Terrorist Action against French Patriots, H-5050; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - French Document Book: Extermination of Innocent Populations, H-5051; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - French Document Book: The Germanization of Western Europe - Introduction, H-5055; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - French Document Book: The Germanization of Western Europe - Annexed Territories Eupen, Malmedy and Moresnet, H-5057; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - French Document Book: The Germanization of Western Europe - Annexed Territories Alsace & Lorraine, H-5059; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - French Document Book: The Germanization of Western Europe - Annexed Territories Luxembourg, H-5061; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - French Document Book: The Germanization of Western Europe - Seizure of Sovereignty - Denmark, H-5064; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) 198 pages
  - French Document Book: The Germanization of Western Europe - The Seizure of Sovereignty - Norway and the Netherlands, H-5066; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - French Document Book: The Germanization of Western Europe - Seizure of Sovereignty - France, H-5069; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - French Document Book: Spiritual Germanization (Propaganda), H-5071; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - French Document Book: Direct Application of Propaganda, H-5073; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - French Document Book (RF) 1200, H-5075; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - French Document Book: The Germanization of Western Europe - Organization of Criminal Activities, H-5076; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - French Document Book: Pillage of Works of Art 1., H-5078; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - French Document Book: Pillage of Works of Art 2., H-5079; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - French Document Book: Document cited by Mr. P. Mounier, H-5081; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - French Document Book: KEITEL & JODL, H-5083; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - French Document Book: Cross-examination of SAUCKEL, H-5117; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s)
  - French Document Book: Cross-examination of SAUCKEL (extracts), H-5118; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) pp. 1-26 plus cover-page
  - French Document Book: RF Exhibits on Cross-examination, H-5119; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) 96 pages
  - USSR Document Books 1 & 2, H-5148; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) pp. 1-53 plus cover page and one-page Errata Sheet
  - USSR Document Book 3, H-5149; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) pp. 1-73 plus cover page
  - USSR Document Books 4 & 5, H-5150; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) pp. 1-66 plus cover page and one-page Errata Sheet, pp. 67-112 plus cover page
  - USSR Document Books 5a & 5b, H-5151; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) pp. 1-97 and 130-262
  - USSR Document Books 6 & 6a, H-5152; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) pp. 1-94 plus cover page and Table of Contents
  - USSR Document Book 7, H-5153; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) pp. 1-48 plus cover page and Table of Contents
  - USSR Document Book 8, H-5154; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) pp. 1-53 plus cover page (English), pp. 1-78 plus cover page (Russian)
  - USA Document Book: USA Documents Submitted on Cross-examination, H-5241; International Military Tribunal; 1 item(s) 595 loose pages